嗯弟弟怎么了吗
啊外面下雨打雷了
很害怕想要姐姐陪你
弟弟你都多大了
还怕下雨打雷
不是说自己是男子汉吗
应该保护姐姐才对
好好
谁让我是你姐姐呢
你先快到被窝里来
外面凉
别把我的好弟弟冻着了
摸摸头
姐姐不是在这里陪你吗
别害羞啦
快来靠近些
被子都要被你扯走了
自己说要和姐姐一起睡
又离我那么远
干嘛
弟弟长大了呢
也到了青春期懵懂的年纪了
不过在我这里永远都是长不大的小孩子哦
怎么把头扭过去了
又害羞了
看着姐姐
我们都好久没有这样一起睡过了
今天弟弟主动来
也给了我一个惊喜呢
怎么了
还很冷吗
到姐姐睡过的地方来
JULIA和点
手都那么冰凉了
姐姐帮你捂捂暖和一下
还说不用手都快冻僵了
是不是又偷偷在打游戏不睡觉
这会儿才来找姐姐
唉你知道我宠你了
就尽管撒娇吧
不过我还是要说一句
以后不准再熬这么晚了
白天玩不也一样吗
也不是讨厌啦
姐姐当然是喜欢你的
可是你也要听姐姐话啊
不然下次可就不让你和我睡了
姐姐和游戏看你怎么选
哈哈真乖
再把你抱紧一点吧
多分些提问给你
快点暖和起来吧
好啦别乱动了
这样在姐姐怀里睡吧
睡不着
要听我讲故事
这这还真难倒我了
我从来没有过这种经历呀
弟弟你可真够坏的
当然不行啦
这个要求我可满足不了
你还是像小时候一样
我陪你数羊吧
嗯这才乖嘛
把眼睛闭上
枕在我怀里
放空自己的大脑
什么也不用想
什么也不用做放松
让自己的四肢变得轻盈
开始咯
一只羊
两只羊
三只羊
四只羊
五只羊
六只羊
七只羊
八只羊
九只羊
十只羊
弟弟
弟弟你睡了吗
蜷缩在怀里像只小猫呢
有点忍不住想挠挠下巴了
看样子是睡着了呢
只剩轻微的喘气声了
也不知道做了什么美梦呢
小嘴还在笑
梦到姐姐我了吗
臭弟弟
弟弟也长大了
不像小时候去哪里都要跟着我了
明明是该为你高兴的事
我却又感到忧愁
是怎么回事
弟弟还真是个小坏蛋
也不知道你在梦里能不能听到姐姐
我还想你能像从前一样粘着我呢
自从长大了就莫名开始疏远姐姐
好不容易主动来找姐姐
结果就为了我哄你入睡
你还真不客气啊
不过没关系
姐姐我会永远陪在你身边的
不管是现在还是未来
姐姐都会是你的依靠
安心吧
那么晚安啦
滴滴
♪ You set yourself apart from the rain ♪
♪ You like the nervousness in my chase ♪
♪ You're the way ♪
♪ I lose my breath ♪
♪ You're the one was there when there's nothing left ♪
♪ You set yourself apart from the race ♪
♪ You like the narrow lain my chest ♪
♪ You're the way ♪
♪ I lose my breath ♪
♪ You're the one ♪
♪ Who style when there's no light come a little closer ♪
♪ Don't be scared ♪
♪ I want you smiling back at me ♪
♪ Hands in my hair ♪
♪ Come a little closer baby ♪
♪ Why i don't shut come a little closer ♪
♪ Come a little closer ♪
♪ Don't be scared ♪
♪ I want you smiling back at me hands in my hair ♪
♪ Got my little closet baby ♪
♪ Why don't shine ♪
♪ I'm a little cross side ♪
♪ You're a common character in my dreams ♪
♪ I wish that you can see that you are song into my memory ♪
♪ Have you word that i s can you hear it in the melody ♪
♪ I will say you will open up to me ♪
♪ Can you hear in my melody ♪
♪ I always say you had open up to me ♪
♪ Come on with the closer ♪
♪ You don't be scared once ♪
♪ You sling back in my hands ♪
♪ In my head on a little closer baby ♪
♪ Why don't shut ♪
♪ Little closer ♪
♪ Don't be scared ♪
♪ I want you smiling back ♪
♪ And we hands in my hair ♪
♪ Come a little closer baby ♪
♪ Why don't shine come a little closet ♪
♪ You say your soul ♪
♪ I'll buy or bite from ♪
♪ You're like that ♪
♪ Nn ♪
♪ Hit i am i am my chase ♪
♪ Hit my chase ♪